<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-24T17:00:26+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Live Laugh LOVE!</title><subtitle>Are you in search for some feel-good love, then Live Laugh LOVE! is your answer. Lovely people rated this blog 10/10. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">About the Author</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/2020/04/17/rens.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About the Author" /><published>2020-04-17T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-17T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/2020/04/17/rens</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/2020/04/17/rens.html">&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; media=&quot;all&quot; href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/stylesheet.css&quot; /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-meta&quot;&gt;
   
     
        1
     
         minute to read.
     
   &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rens is a gentle secretary at a law firm who is obsessed with the murder of his brother Anika, five years ago&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rens Groot is a 29-year-old secretary at a law firm whose life is dominated by solving the murder of his brother, Anika Lewis. Anika was stabbed in 2015 and the killer was never brought to justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is Dutch. He started studying law at college but never finished the course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Physically, Rens is in pretty good shape. He is average-height with fair skin, auburn hair and brown eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He grew up in a middle class neighbourhood. His father left when he was young, leaving him with his mother, who was an addict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is currently in a relationship with Felix Max Moss. Felix is 15 years older than him and works as a management consultant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rens’s best friend is a secretary at a law firm called Esther Scott. They get on well most of the time. He also hangs around with Filip Duncan and Denise Haynes. They enjoy bridge together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This random biography is made using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.character-generator.org.uk/bio/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;character generator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/assets/rens.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;rens&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/assets/loveyou.svg&quot; alt=&quot;loveyou&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; media=&quot;all&quot; href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/stylesheet.css&quot; /&gt;

&lt;nav&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/&quot;&gt;Home&lt;/a&gt;.      
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/page2.html&quot;&gt;Stories&lt;/a&gt;.     
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/page3.html&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/a&gt;.     
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/zelfgemaakt.html&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;.     
&lt;/nav&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quarantine</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/jekyll/update/2020/04/10/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quarantine" /><published>2020-04-10T14:32:32+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-10T14:32:32+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/jekyll/update/2020/04/10/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/jekyll/update/2020/04/10/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;div class=&quot;post-meta&quot;&gt;
   
     
        5
     
         minutes to read.
     
   &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How to Be OK With Being Alone Right Now&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being comfortable by yourself is hard, especially during this pandemic—but there are ways to make it feel a little easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social distancing and sheltering in place during a pandemic is a big emotional undertaking, even if you live with someone you absolutely adore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can be even more difficult if you’re doing it alone, especially if you wish you weren’t. Like, Oh, you don’t like working from home alongside your significant other? Cool—I’m worried about not touching another human for the next three months and dying alone, but go off, I guess!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being comfortable being alone is really hard—especially in these circumstances—but it’s also a skill you can cultivate (even in these circumstances). If you’re social distancing alone right now and hating it, here are some ways to navigate the biggest challenges, and some tips to keep in mind over the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Make a distinction being alone, loneliness, and solitude.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s definitely overlap between these three concepts, but they have different solutions, and it’s helpful to know what you’re working with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being alone, generally speaking, means being physically by yourself. (If you live with a roommate who you’re not really friends with, or you are dating someone but they aren’t nearby, you may feel like you are functionally alone right now, and might also find this article helpful.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Loneliness is a feeling that can set in regardless of how alone you are. It often feels like not really being known: not having anyone to talk to in your city, at your new job, from your couch in quarantine, and/or not having a deep-shallow person who you can be totally yourself with and talk to about every little mundane detail of your day. Humans ultimately need some social connection to feel good and right—even humans who are comfortable with a lot of alone time—so it’s important to be proactive in addressing any loneliness you’re feeling right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solitude is what Lead Yourself First authors Raymond Kethledge and Michael Erwin define as “a subjective state of mind in which the mind, isolated from input from other minds, works through a problem on its own.” Solitude is about being truly alone with your thoughts—so, not being on your phone or in conversation with other people, not texting or tweeting constantly, not even watching TV or reading a book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The capacity for solitude is naturally inhibited by loneliness, which is why it’s important to think about both right now. The good news is that solitude is a buildable skill. So if you dread being physically alone (or not having your phone on you), or worry that not having a relationship or a friend group says something about you or your overall worth, solitude might be the thing to get “good” at. (More on how to do this in a bit.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;If you’re feeling lonely, tell people that.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can be hard to be vulnerable with other people, but if there was ever a time… it’s this moment, when we’re literally all vulnerable. You’re definitely not the only person who’s figuring out how to be away from others right now, and telling people that can be a huge relief, make it possible for them to step in and show up for you, and demonstrate to those you care about that they’re allowed and encouraged to talk about these things if they’re feeling them, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be surprised by how many people will be more responsive to a clear expression of a feeling versus you trying to “show” that you’re lonely in indirect ways (“I’m so bored lmao haven’t talked to anyone in days”). So often, our needs aren’t nearly as obvious as we think they are; if you haven’t used the word “lonely” yet, make a point to do that ASAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/assets/blog.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;When it comes to communication, prioritize quality over quantity.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be tempted to spend a lot of time on social media, where, theoretically, there are always people to “talk to.” But passively receiving updates and interacting in small snippets with loose acquaintances takes time and energy that might be better spent deepening more established relationships (even relatively new ones). Part of building the solitude skill is learning to deal more directly with loneliness, so you can create space for yourself to comfortably be alone, in actual solitude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of logging onto Facebook or sending a mass text every time you feel lonely, think about the two or five or 10 people who really matter to you, and make it a priority to connect with them via a phone call, FaceTime, or Zoom happy hour in the coming weeks. These conversations can be short and don’t have to be deep or serious to be “meaningful.” Joking around and shooting the shit with your co-worker pals can go a long way. (And if you still have time for social media conversations after this, great!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also worth considering how creating content—status updates, IG stories, tweets, texts—can stand in the way of feeling OK with solitude. The more you post, the more responses you’re going to get… which is going to lead to spending more time on apps overall. You’re not really alone with your thoughts, observations, and experiences—aka, experiencing solitude—when you’re posting, so pausing your output for an hour or a half-day can be another effective way to practice feeling chill with being on your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/assets/lips.svg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; media=&quot;all&quot; href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/stylesheet.css&quot; /&gt;

&lt;nav&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/&quot;&gt;Home&lt;/a&gt;.      
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/page2.html&quot;&gt;Stories&lt;/a&gt;.     
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/page3.html&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/a&gt;.     
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/zelfgemaakt.html&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;.     
&lt;/nav&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Online Dating</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/2020/04/10/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Online Dating" /><published>2020-04-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/2020/04/10/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog-renzepensert/2020/04/10/first-post.html">&lt;div class=&quot;post-meta&quot;&gt;
   
     
        2
     
         minutes to read.
     
   &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brands at the new frontier for digital dating are the apps that once connected singles in the physical world, through digital conversations. With the newly enforced norms of physical distancing, they’ve all similarly pivoted to encouraging video chat dating, making certain once-premium features free, and offering tips on the ways prospective daters can adapt to a digital dating landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;Tinder&lt;/span&gt; made their Passport feature (unlimited connections with no physical distance restrictions) temporarily free to encourage global romantic connections in our new world where physical distance is more important than ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;Match&lt;/span&gt; has launched the ‘Dating While Distancing Hotline’, a free service where daters can chat with a live expert for free about their concerns and anxieties of dating in a digital world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;Grindr&lt;/span&gt; took a slightly different approach, instead opting to provide dating-adjacent entertainment, such as sharing steamy hook-up stories, inspirational and uplifting content, and even op-eds around the new role of pornography in the contactless reality of quarantine.
Overall, dating app brands are taking a fairly uniform approach to quarantine dating, but the real opportunities will likely lie in the uncharted territories of the post-COVID world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Post-COVID 19 World Will Be More Online Than Ever Before
Once things begin to return to a semblance of normalcy, the hesitations around meeting new people in the physical world will likely linger for some time. We could see an increase in people going through additional measures to vet their matches before meeting up in person, and an even greater scrutiny on the locations and activities they’re willing to do until the dust truly settles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This discerning approach to potential romantic partners may have even longer lasting effects. One possibility is a rise in pre-date video chats where people get a sense of whether a match is worth leaving the house for. While this may be especially useful in the immediate post-COVID future, it may continue to be a useful tactic for busy business professionals whose time and energy is at a premium; avoiding wasting valuable time and money meeting with someone who turns out to be entirely incompatible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For brands in the business of dating technology, creating social content around these new rules of engagement, and giving them creative tools to navigate this new dating landscape could help alleviate some of those anxieties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/assets/lovebirds.svg&quot; alt=&quot;virus&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; media=&quot;all&quot; href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/stylesheet.css&quot; /&gt;

&lt;nav&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/&quot;&gt;Home&lt;/a&gt;.      
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/page2.html&quot;&gt;Stories&lt;/a&gt;.     
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/page3.html&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/a&gt;.     
	&lt;a href=&quot;/blog-renzepensert/zelfgemaakt.html&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;.     
&lt;/nav&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>